[
    { 
        "question": "1.  What is the past tense of the verb go?:",
        "options": ["A. Goes", "B. Gone", "C. Went", "D. Going"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "2.  Which of the following is the synonym for happy?: ",
        "options": ["A. Sad", "B. Angry", "C. Joyful", "D. Tired"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "3.  What is a synonym for the word exhilarating?: ",
        "options": ["A. Boring", "B. Exciting", "C. Calm", "D. Depressing"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "4.  She ____ to the gym every morning.: ",
        "options": ["A. go", "B. going", "C. goes", "D. gone"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "5.  Choose the correct word to complete the sentence: Her speech was full of _______ quotes.: ",
        "options": ["A. Inspiring", "B. Inspiration", "C. Inspire", "D. Inspired"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.  Which of the following sentences correctly uses a semicolon?: ",
        "options": ["A.  I have a big test tomorrow; I can't go out tonight", "B. I have a big test tomorrow, I can't go out tonight", "C. I have a big test tomorrow; and I can't go out tonight", "D. I have a big test tomorrow: I can't go out tonight"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "7.  Which transition word best fits the sentence? (She was tired; _______, she continued working.):",
        "options": ["A.  However", "B. Because", "C. Therefore", "D. Before"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "8.  Subject-Verb Agreement: Which sentence is grammatically correct?: ",
        "options": ["A. The team of players are ready for the match", "B. The team of players is ready for the match", "C. The team of players were ready for the match", "D. The team of players be ready for the match"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "9.  Pronoun-Antecedent Agreement: Choose the sentence that correctly uses pronoun-antecedent agreement.: ",
        "options": ["A. Each of the students must submit their homework on time", "B. Each of the students must submit his or her homework on time", "C. Each of the students must submit its homework on time", "D. Each of the students must submit they homework on time"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "10.  Modifiers: Which sentence correctly places the modifier?: ",
        "options": ["A. Running quickly, the finish line was reached by the athlete", "B. The athlete, running quickly, reached the finish line", "C. The finish line was reached by the athlete running quickly", "D. Running quickly, the athlete reached the finish line"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "11.  Parallel Structure: Identify the sentence that uses parallel structure correctly.: ",
        "options": ["A. She likes reading, to jog, and watching movies", "B. She likes to read, jogging, and to watch movies", "C. She likes reading, jogging, and watching movies", "D. She likes to read, to jog, and watching movies"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "12.  Active vs. Passive Voice: Which sentence is in the active voice?: ",
        "options": ["A.  The cake was eaten by the children", "B. The children ate the cake", "C. The cake by the children was eaten", "D. By the children, the cake was eaten"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "13.  Is one a number?",
        "options": ["T.True", "F.False"],
        "answer": "T"
    }
]
